

Md. Saiful Islam Tusher

Phone: 01686929888

Address: 119,kawla ,Dakshikhan,Dhaka-1229
Website: https://www.facebook.com/ripazhalinksaiful

Email: bmcgsaiful2019@gmail.com

Dear Sir,

I'm Saiful Islam Tusher,I belong to kwala,Dakshinkhan Dhaka-1229.I completed my graduation under national university major subject was Management. My Institute name is A.K.M Rahamatullah University. Founded by EX MP A.K.M Rahamatullah Sir .I'm not a fresher. I'm carrying an experience approximately 5 years in customer service and in Sales & marketing Department. I worked in Service solution private limited(citycell) as a customer service Representative. I worked in genex infosy's (grameen phone) as a Customer Support Executive. I Worked in augere wireless broadband bangladesh limited (qubee) as a (Marketing Executive and Customer Relationship Manager). I worked in Ammazan Stock Lot(Marketing executive). I worked in BMC GROUP as a marketing coordinator .Maybe i will be new here but you don't worry i'm qualified and flexible for any job within my qualification .I will not take long time to understand my responsibilities .I can assure you that I'm capable and I'm passionate about my career .If i tell you about my last jobs Performance then must i want to tell you i was one of the best performer .I should tell you about my duty times It was 11 hour for per day. I really a hard worker person .For More information open my resume Please .It's my humble request to you give me a chance.

Therefore pray, and I hope that you will give me a opportunity and you will appoint me as soon as possible for this position or any comfortable position within my qualification and experience.

Thank you & Your Sincerely

Md. Saiful Islam Tusher sifulislamtuser1@gmail.com khazasaifulchisty@hotmail.com

Mobile:01686929888

Md. Saiful Islam Tusher

Phone: 01686929888

Address: 119, kawla, Dakshikhan, Dhaka-1229

Website:https://www.facebook.com/ripazhalinksaiful

Email:bmcgsaiful2019@gmail.com

To be efficient and successful in a higher position in the field of work and build up a strong career with a renowned organization. I am especially interested in a position with the potential for advancement and increased administration support and responsibilities, which will apply my work background and experience in the activities and thus the organization, will have benefited from my initiative capabilities and contribution. You are the judge; you have the judgment what's your need, an experienced person who can give you the best.

EXPERIENCE

Service solution private limited (SSL)

07/12/2014 - 09/08/2016

Customers Service Executive

Answer incoming calls and respond to customer's emails. Management and resolve customer complaints. Sell products and place customer orders in the computer system. Identify and escalate issues to supervisors. Provide product and service information to customers. Research required information using available resources. Research, identify, and resolve customer complaints using applicable software. Process orders, forms, and application. Route calls to appropriate resources. Document all call information according to standard operating procedures. Recognize, document, and alert the management team of trends in customer calls. Follow up customer calls where necessary. Up sell products and services. Complete call logs and reports. Other duties as assigned. Data Entry .ETC

Genex Infosys 01/09/2016 - 16/11/2016

Customers Support Executive

Answer incoming calls and respond to customer's emails. Management and resolve customer complaints. Sell products and place customer orders in the computer system. Identify and escalate issues to supervisors. Provide product and service information to customers. Research required information using available resources. Research, identify, and resolve customer complaints using applicable software. Process orders, forms, and application. Route calls to appropriate resources. Document all call information according to standard operating procedures. Recognize, document, and alert the management team of trends in customer calls. Follow up customer calls where necessary. Up sell products and services. Complete call logs and reports. Other duties as assigned. Data Entry .ETC

Augere wireless Broadband Bangladesh Limited (Qubee)

17/11/2016 - 01/07/2018

Customers Support Executive

Answer incoming calls and respond to customer's emails. Management and resolve customer complaints. Sell products and place customer orders in the computer system. Identify and escalate issues to supervisors. Provide product and service information to customers. Research required information using available resources. Research, identify, and resolve customer complaints using applicable software. Process orders, forms, and application. Route calls to appropriate resources. Document all call information according to standard operating procedures. Recognize, document, and alert the management team of trends in customer calls. Follow up customer calls where necessary. Up sell products and services. Complete call logs and reports. Other duties as assigned. Data Entry (Floor Support Absent Of supervisors).ETC

Ammazan stock lot

07/07/2018 - 20//06/2019

Business Development Executive

Communication with online client and Face to face Communication. Field Marketing In Market.

Dealing with wholesale and retail buyers, showroom buyers, online buyers, order observation,

Products output and input entry. Calculation of Sales Collection and costs. Assign SR. Monitoring Team

EDUCATION

Civil Aviation High School

2011

Exam: Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C.)

Result: 3.81(in the scale of 5.00)

Institution: Uttara Town University College

2013

Exam: Higher Secondary School Certificate (H.S.C),

Result: 3.70 (in scale of 5.00)

A.K.M Rahamatullah College University

2019

Bachelor of Business Administration (Management) (B.B.A.),

Result: 2.73 (in scale of 4.00)

SKILLS

COMPUTERSKILL:

Operating Systems:

Windows 98, Windows XP, Windows 7, Vista, & 8.

Applications:

MS Word (Good Typing speed), MS Excel, Data Analysis, Databases work.

Internet & Others:

Efficient in internet handling, PC Hardware & Software Knowledge, Web Browsing.

LANGUAGES

English (Good), Bangla (Good), Hindi (Good)

AREA OF INTEREST:

AREA OF INTEREST:

L e arn more work. Special interest in traveling.

Making friendship. Organizing activities.

Browsing Internet .Learn to run different software.

Playing Online Game, Playing PC Game, Watching Movie, Riding Bike, Driving Car,

CookingFood and Dessert.

STRENGTHS:

STRENGTHS:

Good capability in face to face, over the phone and mailing communication. Good academic record. Ambitious and target oriented and confident. Innovative, Dynamics and self-motivates. Organizational Skills, Able to work under pressure. Man power Controlling Power. Hard working, Team work, Leadership Power. System Friendly, Honesty, Ambition and a Strong Work Ethic.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal Information

Father's Name: Md. HarunOrRashid
Mother's Name: Sahanaz begum
Date of Birth: 11st november,1995
Nationality: Bangladeshi (Bybirth)

Religion: Islam

Marital Status: Unmarried Blood Group: AB (+ve)



Ref: TRMC/HRD/EC CC

Date: 29-07-2018

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

This is to certify that Md. Siful Islam Tusher served as Hourly Paid Contract Employee in TRMC (Total Resource Management Consultant) from 17th November 2016 to 30th June 2018. His designation was "Trainee", Call Centre, Customer Services Department, in the Augere Wireless Broadband Bangladesh Ltd (QUBEE).

During the job contract period he remained involved dedicatedly. We found Md. Siful Islam Tusher pretty active in whatever tasks were assigned. He seems to be confident, hard-working and a devoted employee. He has the motivation to take initiative for new/challenging assignments and we are gratified that he had been helpful in the advancement of the organization.

We wish his all best successes in life.





Date: November 21, 2016

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

This is to certify that Mr. Md. Siful Islam Tuser, son of Mr. Md. Harun Or Rashid, 119, Kawlar Shiyaldanga, P.O. : Khilkhat, P.S. : Dokkhin Khan, Dist. : Dhaka-1229 has been serving in this company as an "Call Center Agent" under part time contract since December 07, 2014 to December 20, 2016. Mr. Tuser has resigned from the company effective from August 09, 2016 at his own accord.

He has discharged his responsibilities with full satisfaction.

We wish him every success in future life.

A. F. M. Moniruzzaman

Human Resources & Administration

SAIFUL ISLAM TUSER

Signature:

Date: